{"data":[{"question":"________ there is a close correlation between stress and illness.","a":"Some psychologists believe","b":"Believed some psychologists","c":"Some psychologists to believe","d":"Some psychologists believing","answer":"1","explain":"\n- People\/ They + think\/ say\/ suppose\/ believe\/ consider\/ report ... + (THAT )+ clause.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"________ is often used in soups and sauces.","a":"Parsley, an inexpensive herb,","b":"Parsley is an inexpensive herb","c":"Inexpensive parsley, herb","d":"An herb is inexpensive parsley","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Use a pair of commas in the middle of a sentence to set off clauses, phrases, and words that are not essential to the meaning of the sentence.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Perspiration increases ________ vigorous exercise or hot weather.","a":"during","b":"when","c":"at the time","d":"for","answer":"1","explain":"\n- When + Clause; at the time + that\/clause.\u00a0\n- During + period.\u00a0\n- For: implies purpose.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Goddard developed the first rocket to fly faster ________.","a":"than sound is","b":"does sound","c":"sound","d":"than sound","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Comparative of adj:\u00a0\n+ Short adj: Adj + er + than.\u00a0\n+ Long adj: More + adj + than.\u00a0\n- Fly: is normal verb- \"is\" is not correct (it should be \"to do\").\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Even if the unemployment rate ________ sharply, the drop may still be temporary.","a":"to drop","b":"dropping","c":"have dropped","d":"drops","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use the conditional sentence type I","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Studies indicate ________ collecting art today than ever before.","a":"there are that more people","b":"more people that are","c":"that there are more people","d":"people there are more","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Indicate\/believe ...that.\u00a0\n- We use the comparative form of short adjectives much","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Thieu Tri was a ________ poet who would pen a verse or two at a moment's notice.","a":"prolific","b":"prolifically","c":"prolificacy","d":"prolificity","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A ............... poet is a noun phrase- we need an adj or a noun in .... \n- In this case, we should use adj.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"I've been to the theater ________ of times.","a":"much","b":"a little","c":"most of","d":"few","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Much\/ a little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"But ________ of the plays I've seen are modern.","a":"a few of","b":"a little","c":"most","d":"many","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Much \/ a little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.\u00a0\n- Most of: nearly all of the people or things in a group, or nearly all of something.\u00a0\n- In this case \" most\" is more suitable than \"many\" because speaker wants to express \"nearly all of the plays\".","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"When I studied Shakespeare, I thought his plays were ________ boring.","a":"a great deal of","b":"few","c":"much","d":"many","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A great deal of\/ many\/few+ noun.\n- Much + noun\/adj.\u00a0\n- Much \/ a little\/ : uncountable noun\/ adj.\u00a0\n- A great deal of + uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"}]}